<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Kanpur Guide
    </string>

    <string name="climate_intro">
        The climate of Kanpur is feisty. The summers are hot and dry which last for four months,
from March to June. The summers are immediately followed by the monsoon season which lasts from
July to September. The following two months are warm, humid and sultry. This is followed by the
onset of winters which prevails till the mid of February. The average summer temperature is about 32 C
which peaks at 44 C. The average winter temperature ranges from 15 C to 18 C. The night temperatures
in winter may drop to as low as 3 C. The bulk of the precipitation in Kanpur occurs during the
monsoon season, the average rainfall during the year being 960mm.
    </string>

    <string name="breakfast_intro">
        Hungry? Want to have some breakfast, Kanpur Style? Here
are some curated restaurants and  popular food brands
for you which serve according to the whims of your tongue. You wont
find anything better in this town. Choose your food slave for the morning
from the following picks .
    </string>

    <string name="lunch_intro">
        Had a tiring morning? Too stressed out? Or Just want to have a good meal this afternoon?
You\'ve come to the right place. Kanpur is filled with edible delight. But you\'ve got to know the
right place in the town. Here are four affordable restaurants for you where you could enjoy
a sumptuous meal this afternoon. Check these out. And hey, have a fine afternoon .
    </string>

    <string name="dinner_intro">
        Want to have a rich dining experience in Kanpur? And make it affordable? Well, we have the
picks for you. These restaurants boast of the best dining experiences in the city. Have a dinner date
or a whim to dine with the family? Cawpore 1857, Waterside and Terrazza 9 are places for you.
Best of luck exploring these diners !
    </string>

    <string name="travel_intro">
        Kanpur is one of the oldest cities in India. Situated on the banks of the river
Ganga, Kanpur is a rich blend of culture, tradition and youth. Thousands of tourists visit Kanpur
every year to experience the splendor of the one of a kind historical and religious sites located
here. From many a choices, we\'ve collected the top 3 tourist attractions of the city for you.
Happy sightseeing .
    </string>

</resources>
