<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Kanpur Guide
    </string>

    <string name="climate_intro">
        The climate of Kanpur is feisty. The summers are hot and dry which last for four months,
from March to June. The summers are immediately followed by the monsoon season which lasts from
July to September. The following two months are warm, humid and sultry. This is followed by the
onset of winters which prevails till the mid of February. The average summer temperature is about 32 C
which peaks at 44 C. The average winter temperature ranges from 15 C to 18 C. The night temperatures
in winter may drop to as low as 3 C. The bulk of the precipitation in Kanpur occurs during the
monsoon season, the average rainfall during the year being 960mm.
    </string>

    <string name="breakfast_intro">
        Hungry? Want to have some breakfast, Kanpur Style? Here
are some curated restaurants and  popular food brands
for you which serve according to the whims of your tongue. You wont
find anything better in this town. Choose your food slave for the morning
from the following picks .
    </string>

    <string name="lunch_intro">
        Had a tiring morning? Too stressed out? Or Just want to have a good meal this afternoon?
You\'ve come to the right place. Kanpur is filled with edible delight. But you\'ve got to know the
right place in the town. Here are four affordable restaurants for you where you could enjoy
a sumptuous meal this afternoon. Check these out. And hey, have a fine afternoon .
    </string>

    <string name="dinner_intro">
        Want to have a rich dining experience in Kanpur? And make it affordable? Well, we have the
picks for you. These restaurants boast of the best dining experiences in the city. Have a dinner date
or a whim to dine with the family? Cawpore 1857, Waterside and Terrazza 9 are places for you.
Best of luck exploring these diners !
    </string>

    <string name="travel_intro">
        Kanpur is one of the oldest cities in India. Situated on the banks of the river
Ganga, Kanpur is a rich blend of culture, tradition and youth. Thousands of tourists visit Kanpur
every year to experience the splendor of the one of a kind historical and religious sites located
here. From many a choices, we\'ve collected the top 4 tourist attractions of the city for you.
Happy sightseeing .
    </string>

    <string name="bithoor_intro">
        Located around 23 km from Kanpur,Bithoor (once known as Brahmavart) is a very important site
for both Hindu religion and Indian history at large. Legend has it that after the destruction of the
universe and reconstruction of the galaxy by Lord Vishnu, Lord Brahma (the creator of the universe)
 selected Bithoor as his abode and performed a \'yagna\'(Hindu prayer ceremony) here, naming the town as
Brahmavart. This town was also one of the epicenters of revolt of 1857. During the First War of Independence
, Bithoor became a rallying point for the rebellion against the British East India Company, until it was
captured by General Havelock in 1857. Today, Bithoor attracts a large number of pilgrims who visit
the Brahmavart Ghat and Valmiki Ashram, which are the primary attractions of the town .
    </string>

    <string name="allenforrestzoo_intro">
        The Allen Forest Zoo, also known simply as the Kanpur Zoo, is the largest open green space in Kanpur. The zoo was founded by
Sir Allen, a botanist and a member of the British Indian Civil Service, and opened to the public in 1971. The grounds encompass a gorgeous
lake, and a forest full of ancient trees. This zoo is home to a broad range of mammals, such as rare big cats like Whie Asian tigers,
Asiatic lions, leopards and jaguars, and a range of monkeys and primates like chimpanzees, baboons, and orangutans. The zoo also houses
an aquarium, as well life size sculptures of prehistoric dinasours. Those looking to explore the natural beauty of the zoo can join
the zoo\'s staff on regularly conducted nature walks and a variety of other outdoor recreational activities .
    </string>

    <string name="iscon_intro">
        The ISCON / ISKCON temple or Sri Sri Radha Madhav Mandir in Kanpur is the second largest in the world only after the Mayapur ISKON
temple in West Bengal. Opened for devotees in 2014, the beautiful temple attracts thousands of devotees and visitors every year. The
temple is spread out over fifteen acres of land. The compound also includes a Vedic Ashram, Food for Life center, Bhaktivedanta Youth Academy
, Bhaktivedanta Book Library, a guest house for devotees, a conference room, community hall, a restaurant and a gift shop. It also includes
a Goshala which houses over sixty cows.
    </string>

    <string name="blueworld_intro">
        One of the iconic landmarks of the city is the renowned Blue World Theme Park. An entertainment choice of vacationers, this
amusement park is packed with adventurous water rides and spectacular shows including flying carousel, revolving tower and jumping frog
ride. One of the key attractions of this place is the water laser show which involves projection filming on a water screen. Other attractions
include Western train rides, Jet Planes, Columbus and Ferris wheel. Featuring around 10 huge slides and 25 stimulating rides, it is a must
visit destination for all travellers visiting Kanpur .
    </string>
    
    <string name="history_intro">
        The history of Kanpur dates back to the 13th century, when the present-day Kanpur was a village named
Kanhpur, established by Raja Kanh Deo of the Kanhpuria clan. The area was ruled by several rulers of
Kannauj, such as Harsha Vardhan, Jai Chand and Mihir Bhoja. It was also ruled by Muslim rulers of the
Sur dynasty. In May 1765, Shuja-ud-daula, the Nawab of Awadh, was defeated by the British near Jajmau.
From 1773 to 1801, Kanpur was part of the Oudh kingdom, followed by the treaty of 1801 between Nawab
Saadat Ali Khan of Awadh and the British, who realized the strategic importance of Kanpur. Several
Europen businessmen established themselves in Kanpur, during this time. The city took part in the Indian
Rebellion of 1857, under Nana Sahib. Certain events led to the Bibighar massacre, when the sepoy forces
killed 120 women and children. Following these events, the Kanpur Massacre and similar other massacres was
carried out by the British, as justification. It led to the loss of the lives of several sepoys, as well
as civilian men, women and children. Under the British, the present-day Uttar Pradesh was called as
United Provinces. After the independence of India, it was renamed as Uttar Pradesh in the year 1950.
    </string>

    <string name="culture_intro">
Kanpur is blessed with a rich cultural heritage. Eminent poets such as Bal Krishna Sharma have played a key role in promoting this culture.
Fair and festivals that are celebrated in the city, also offer a glimpse of the culture of Kanpur. The famous Ganga Fair is held for five
days each year, attracting people from all walks of life. Devotees play Holi and take a holy bath in the Ganges. Kanpur has played an important
role in the propagation of ‘Nautanki’, a theatre form. Cultural events such as Ram Lila provide a platform to budding artists.
Classical Indian dance and music forms are also very popular in Kanpur. The food in Kanpur is inspired by Awadhi cuisine. Khoya Laddu and
Biryani are some of the famous delicacies.
    </string>

</resources>
